Happily N'Ever After 2 is a animation, comedy,
adventure film directed by Boyd Kirkland.
Fairy tales collide when Mambo and Munk tip the
scales of good and evil once again.
Little Red Riding Hood (voice), played by G.K. Bowes.
King Cole / Peter / Humpty Dumpty, played by Kelly Brewster.
Pied Piper (voice), played by Doug Erholtz.
Old Woman in Shoe (voice), played by Jennie Fahn.
Snow White (voice), played by Helen Niedwick.
Priest / Rumpelstiltskin (voice), played by David Lodge.
Happily N'Ever After is a 2006 animated fantasy
adventure comedy film directed by Paul J.
Bolger, produced by John H.
Williams, and written by Rob Moreland.
It is inspired by fairy tales of the Brothers Grimm and Hans Christian Andersen and
loosely based on the 1999 animated German television series Simsala Grimm.
The title is the opposite of a stock phrase, happily ever after; the name
is contracted with an apostrophe between the N and the E.
The film stars the voices of Sarah Michelle Gellar, Freddie Prinze, Jr., Andy Dick,
Wallace Shawn, Patrick Warburton, George Carlin, and Sigourney Weaver.
The film was one of Carlin's final works before his death in 2008.
Lionsgate theatrically released Happily N'Ever After in
the United States on January 5, 2007.
The film was panned by critics and grossed $38 million worldwide against a
production budget of $47 million, becoming a box-office bomb.
Despite its negative reviews and poor performance, it was followed by a direct-to-video sequel
in 2009 called Happily N'Ever After 2: Snow White—Another Bite @ the Apple.
The tone is lighthearted.